القائمة

القائمة

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**

Flash Toons built a set of Android Apps and published them for free. This SERVICE is provided by Flash Toons at no cost and is intended for use as is. In addition, Flash Toons published flash-toons.com website.

This page is used to inform our website or Google Play visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

Our website or published apps on Google Play does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app: [Google Play Services](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the website: [Tiwtter](https://twitter.com/en/privacy), [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html), [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on users' browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving our website.

**Log Data**

We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

**Children’s Privacy**

These Services addresses anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

**Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

* To facilitate our Service;
* To provide the Service on our behalf;
* To perform Service-related services; or
* To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through our [contact page](https://flash-toons.com/%d8%a7%d8%aa%d8%b5%d9%84-%d8%a8%d9%86%d8%a7/).

### شارك هذا الموضوع:

**جميع الحقوق محفوظة لفلاش توونز © 2024 - [Privacy Policy](https://flash-toons.com/privacy-policy/ "Privacy Policy") - [Terms of Use](https://flash-toons.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use")**
